If you think you know your lover. Think again. Especially if she's your wife.
Dream Lover is a drama, mystery, thriller film directed by Nicholas Kazan.
Not long after they cross paths at an art gallery, architect Ray Reardon
and hypnotically sensual Lena are married with children.
But as strange incidents occur, Ray begins to realize he
may not really know the woman he married.
Ray Reardon, played by James Spader.
Lena Mathers, played by Mädchen Amick.
Larry, played by Fredric Lehne.
Elaine, played by Bess Armstrong.
Norman, played by Larry Miller.
Martha, played by Kathleen York.
Dream Lover is a 1993 American erotic thriller film written and directed by Nicholas Kazan and starring James
Spader and Mädchen Amick, with Bess Armstrong, Frederic Lehne, and Larry Miller in supporting roles.
The original music score was composed by Christopher Young.
The film explores themes of adultery, paranoia,
architect, marriage, femme fatale.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.